

### **CONTACT ME AT**

Address: Franjo Kluz 9/ 1-62 - Skopje

(0) +38975274395

mihail\_davidevski@outlook.com

in mihail-davidevski

## SKILLS SUMMARY



















## PERSONAL

PROBLEM SOLVING **MULTI-TASKING GREAT COMMUNICATION SKILLS ANALYTICAL SKILLS CREATIVE QUICK LEARNER TEAM WORKER PUNCTUAL** 

# MIHAIL DAVIDEVSKI

## FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm Mihail Davidevski a 27 year old who has a strong passion and interest for web development and coding. I'm extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills, eager to gain experience and learn new things that will help me to grow professionally. I was thought to look at challenges as if they were opportunities to learn.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Pabau

Junior React Developer Skopje | May 2022 - Present

#### Pabau

Junior React Developer Intern Skopje | Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

#### **National Forrest**

Sector for forest management and hunting grounds, and design Skopje | Aug 2018 - Jan 2022

## **Johnson Matthey**

Heels and Washings Operator Skopje | Oct 2017 - May 2018

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

High School - Gymnasium, "Krste Petkov Misirkov"

Graduated engineer of forestry on faculty of forestry 'Hans Em' -Skopje